Guide to the David Sullivan U.S. Maoism Collection TAM 527
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Revolutionary Communist Party, 1975-1982
  - Afro-American Commission, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Agendas, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Avakian, Marcelle, Criticism of, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Beginning Study Group, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Brochures, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins, circa 1976-1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bulletins: District, 1976-1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins: National, 1976-1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins: National, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Bulletins: Security, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Busing, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Central Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Central Committee: Reports, 1976, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Central Committee: Reports (split with Revolutionary Workers Headquarters), undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - China/ Gang of Four, 1975-1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The City Crisis (New York, NY), undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Committee to Free the Mao Tsetung Defendants, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Congress Documents: Committee Reports and Resolutions I, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Congress Documents: Committee Reports and Resolutions II, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Congress Documents: Main Political Report, Majority Report, Minority Report, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Constitution, Report on, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dayton Report: Mass Line, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Fliers, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Founding Celebration, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - International Communist Movement: Draft Position Paper, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - International Women's Day, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Iran, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - July 4th Demonstration, circa 1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Leadership Training Class, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Mao Tsetung (memorial), undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mao Tsetung Memorial Committee, circa 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mass Line (May Day, busing, July 4th), circa 1976 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - May Day, 1977, 1980, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Meeting Notes, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Military Science/ Arming of the Masses, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - National Secretariat: Report, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - National United Workers Organization, circa 1977 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - National Workers Organization/ Intermediate Workers Organization (IWO)/ Area-Wide Workers Organizations, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - New Jersey Workers Organization (Marxist-Leninist), undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Pamphlets, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Pamphlets, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Pamphlets, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Pamphlets, 1980-1981, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Party Branches Article, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Political Education, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Position Papers: "Into the Thick of Things", undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Position Papers: "Revisionists Are Revisionists and Must Not Be Supported...", undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Programme and Constitution (new), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Publicity Materials, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Revolution: Reprint Pamphlets, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Revolutionary Communist Youth Brigade, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - "Revolutionary Work in a Non-Revolutionary Situation", 1978 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Revolutionary Worker, Material Related to, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Revolutionary Workers Headquarters, Split with, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Speech: Two Octobers, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Standing Committee, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Students/ Revolutionary Student Brigade/ Young Communist League, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Study Groups, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Teng Hsiao-Ping/ Deng Xiaoping Visit, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Trade Union Organizing, 1976-1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Unemployment Benefits/ Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - US-China People's Friendship Association, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War/ Veterans, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Reform Bill, Statement on, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Worker, Material Related to, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Worker: Pamphlets, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Workers Study Outline, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - X Work Team Sum Up, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Series III: Revolutionary Workers Headquarters, 1977-1984
  Series III contains material generated by and about the Revolutionary Workers Headquarters, a faction of the Revolutionary Communist Party that broke away following the downfall of the Gang of Four in China in 1976. Material in this Series dates from the organization's formation in 1977, including its paper Voices of the Rebellion, which announces the group's separation from the RCP and goes through 1984. In this Series, material is divided by district, committee, and regional as well as by topic and format. While a portion of this Series is printed and public, including district and national bulletins, fliers, journals, and pamphlets, the majority consists of internal documents. Folders contain drafts and memos on such pertinent topics as, agitation and propaganda relating to the development of a organizational newspaper, the black national question, busing in Boston, Cook County Hospital, the equal rights amendment, fusion between the workers movement and the social movement, the international situation mostly pertaining to the situation in China following the death of Mao Tsetung and the Three Worlds Theory, the national question, and the woman question. Of note are lengthy itineraries, reports, and correspondence from a visit to China in 1979-1980. The Boston, Chicago, and New York City districts are most heavily represented in this Series. Folders outlining the RWH's political campaigns surrounding African Liberation Day and May Day contain fliers and reports. Central to this Series is the RWH's work with uniting Marxist-Leninists in the United States. There are folders outlining lengthy merger discussions with the Bay Area Communist Union, the Communist Party (Marxist-Leninist), the Committee to Unite Marxist Leninists, and the League of Revolutionary Struggle. At times discussions lasted over the course of several years. Heavily important to the RWH was its work in trade unions and the trade union movement. There is a sizable amount of material in this Series, which outlines various trade union strategies and involvement in the auto, electrical, mining, and steel industries.
  - African Liberation Day, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Agendas (unidentified district), 1979-1980, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Agitation and Propaganda, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Anti-Weber Coalition, 1979, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Auto Convention, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Avakian, Bob (report on his visit to a mineworkers strike), undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Baltimore, 1982, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bay Area Communist Union: Merger, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bay Area Work Team for Cambodian Relief, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Beginning Principles and Priorities, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Black National Question, 1980, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Boston District, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Boston District: District Bulletin/ Joint District Bulletin, 1981, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bulletins: District (unidentified), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bulletins: National I, 1978-1982, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bulletins: National II, 1978-1982, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Busing (Boston), undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - The Call, Revolutionary Workers Headquarters Work on, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Central Committee/ Expanded CC, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Chicago District, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Chicago District: Bulletin, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Chicago District: Meetings: Agendas and Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Chicago District: Organization Bulletin, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Chicago District: Reports, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Chicago District: Trade Union Commission, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - China Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Circular Letters, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Citizen's Party, 1980, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Committee to Unite Marxists Leninists, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Communist Party (Marxist-Leninist): Merger, 1979, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Congress, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Congress: Papers Part I, circa 1980 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Congress: Papers Part II, circa 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Congress: Papers Part III, circa 1980 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Cook County Hospital, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Criticism, Struggle, Unity (theoretical journal), 1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Dialectical Materialism, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - East Coast Regional, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - El Salvador, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Energy Question, 1980, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Finances, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fliers, 1981, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fusion (social movement and workers movement) I, 1979, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fusion (social movement and workers movement) II, 1979, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Gang of Four" Paper, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Independent Revolutionary Workers Movement (MOIR) (Colombia), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - International Situation: Conferences, 1971-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - International Situation/ Three Worlds Theory I, 1978-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - International Situation/ Three World Theory II, 1978-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - International Socialists, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - International Women's Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Iran, 1979-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Kampuchea, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lawyers Work, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lawyers Work, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Lawyers Work, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - League of Revolutionary Struggle: Merger/ Unity, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Day Activities, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Marxist-Leninists Merger/ Unity, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - May Day, 1978, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - May Day Work Team, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - McGee, Michael/ United Black Community Council, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Medical Committee for Human Rights, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Meetings: District (unidentified), 1981, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Meetings: Mass, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Meetings: Midwest Revolutionary Workers Headquarters/ Proletarian Unity League and Friends, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Member Profiles/ Biographies, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Milwaukee District, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - National Question, 1979-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - National Question: Study Group, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Nationalities Conference (New York, NY), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital (NCB), undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Nuclear Power, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - NYC District, 1979, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - NY-NJ District Committee, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Organization, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - OSHA/ Health and Safety, 1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Pamphlets, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Party Building, 1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - People Against the Transit Hike, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Peoples Convention, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Philadelphia, 1978-1979, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Pittsburgh District, 1979, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Pole Publications: Correspondence regarding "Build the Black Liberation Movement", 1981 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Political Center, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Political Line, 1978, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Position Papers, 1979-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Professionals Branch, 1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Proletarian Unity League, 1980-1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Rectification/ Rebellion, 1978, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Red Papers 8 (going public with split from Revolutionary Communist Party), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Reports: District: HQ-CPML Joint, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Reports: District (unidentified), 1980-1981, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Reports: District (unidentified), 1990 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Reports: Draft Political (CPML, PUL, and RWH), undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Reports: East Humbolt Park (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Reports: Interim District, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Reports: Joint Political (written by Revolutionary Workers Headquarters and Communist Party (Marxist-Leninist)), undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Reports: Work Summation, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Resignation Letters, 1979-1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sibeko, David Memorial Meeting, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Union, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Speech: "Communist Work in the Trade Unions", 1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Speech: Guardian Celebration, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Student Commission, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Study Groups/ Classes, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Trade Union Work, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Trade Union Work: Auto, 1979, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Trade Union Work: GE, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Trade Union Work: Meetings, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Trade Union Work: Miners, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Trade Union Work: Reports (various industries), undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Trade Union Work: Statistics/ Demographics, circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Trade Union Work: Steel, 1979-1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Trade Union Work: Strategy, 1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Tupelo Activities, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Unemployment Work/ Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - US-China Peoples Friendship Association, 1979-1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Voices of the Rebellion, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Woman Question, 1979, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Women's Commission, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Women's Rights/ Women's Liberation, 1978-1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - The Worker, Material Related to, 1978, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - The Worker: Pamphlets, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - The Workers Voice, Material Related to, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Youth Work/ Students, 1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Series IV: Communist Party (Marxist-Leninist), 1976-1981
  Series IV contains material generated by the Communist Party (Marxist-Leninist) (CPML), which dates from 1976 when the organization changed its name from the October League up through 1981. While there are public and printed documents in this Series in the way of district and national bulletins and pamphlets from The Call and Call Publications, most of the material is internal. A large portion of this Series is made up of reports from various districts and regionals. These consist of page long, occasionally hand-written briefs outlining political campaigns and recruitment work going on in the CPML's districts and regionals around the country. Another sizable portion of this Series consists of notebooks filled with minutes and notes from meetings of the Political Bureau and the Standing Committee. There are a number of folders containing material from the CPML's commissions and fractions, including the Afro-American, National Trade Union, and National Women's Commissions and the Azanian Support, National Lawyers Guild, and the Southern Conference Education Fund Fractions. Of note in this Series is material pertaining to the expulsion of Martin Nicolaus as well as a resignation letter from civil rights activist Lyn Wells. Like Series III, there is material related to various merger negotiations amongst U.S. Marxist-Leninist organizations, including the Revolutionary Workers Headquarters and the New Voice.
  - Afghanistan/ Iran, 1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Afro-American Commission, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Agitation and Propaganda, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Anti-Nuclear Fraction, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Anti-Revisionist Committee, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Article: Davidson, Carl "Lessons from the Collapse of the Communist Party (M-L)", undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Azanian Support Fraction, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Boston District, 1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Bulletins, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Bulletins: Information, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Bulletins: Internal, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Bulletins: Unity (Communist Party (Marxist-Leninist) and Revolutionary Workers Headquarters merger), undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Cadre School, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Cadre School I, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Cadre School II, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Cadre School III, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Cadre School Papers, 1979, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - The Call, Material Related to, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - The Call: Pamphlets and Publications I, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - The Call: Pamphlets and Publications II, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Call Publications, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Central Committee, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Chicago Call Committee: Labor Newspaper Workshop, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Chicago District: Liaison Work with Revolutionary Workers Headquarters, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Chicago District: "You Heard It Through the Grapevine" (official bulletin), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - China Trip, 1980, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committee for Peace in the Eighties, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Communist Youth Organization (CYO), 1977-1979, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Congress (founding), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Congress Preparations, 1980-1981, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Constitution: Draft, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Finances, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "Hinton Line" (William Hinton, U.S. imperialism), undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Intellectual Work, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - International Situation, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - IPC?/ Marxist-Leninist Unity, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Left-Wing Communism, 1980, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Leninism, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Marxist-Leninist Meeting (Atlanta, GA), 1981 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Minutes/ Notes: Notebook I, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Meeting Minutes/ Notes: Notebook II, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Meeting Minutes/ Notes: Notebook III, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Meeting Minutes/ Notes: Notebook I, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Meeting Minutes/ Notes: Notebook II, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - National Asian-American Commission, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - National Chicano Commission, 1979, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - National Communist Youth Organization Fraction, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - National Education Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - National Lawyers Guild/ Legal Fraction, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - National Lawyers Guild Fraction, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - National Liaison Commission, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - National Puerto Rican Commission, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - National Reform Organization, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - National Trade Union Commission, 1979, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - National Women's Commission, 1978-1980, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - The New Voice, Merger with, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - NFBO? Fraction, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Nicolaus, Martin (expelling of), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Nicolaus, Martin: "In Response to the Paper of Oct. 11" (outline criticism of MN's line), undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Nicolaus, Martin Line, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Pamphlets, 1978, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Political Bureau Meeting: Report, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Political Bureau: Notebook I, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Political Bureau: Notebook II, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Political Report Committee, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Political Report, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Political Report: Draft, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Position Papers, 1980, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Position Papers: Democratic Centralism, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Position Papers: National Question, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Position Papers: "What Road for the CPML?", undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Proletarian Unity League, Report on, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Reports: District, Feb-Mar 1979 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Reports: District, Apr 1979 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Reports: District, May 1979 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Reports: District, Jun 1979 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Reports: District, Nov 1979 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Reports: District, Dec 1979 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Reports: District, Jan-Feb 1980 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Reports: District, Mar 1980 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Reports: District, Apr 1980 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Reports: District, May 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Reports: District, Jul 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Reports: District, Aug-Sep 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Reports: District, Oct-Nov 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Reports: District, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Reports: Regional, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Resignation Letters, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Resignation Letters (Wells, Lyn), 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Revolutionary Workers Headquarters: Merger, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Southern Christian Education Fund (SCEF) Fraction, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Spark, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Standing Committee: Draft Evaluation of the Party Leadership, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Standing Committee: Liaison Report on Merger with Revolutionary Workers Headquarters, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Standing Committee: Notebook I, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Standing Committee: Notebook II, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Standing Committee: Notebook III, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Standing Committee: Notebook, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Steel Cadre Meeting, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Summer Camps, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tampa, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Three Evils Meeting/ Campaign, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Trade Union Rag, 1981, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Trade Union Work, 1981, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Ultraleftism, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - United Front, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Women Cadre Meeting, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Series V: Union Organizing, 1961-1988